# Gigi Li

# Student - Fullstack Development



### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a hardworking, loyal and responsible worker who loves to interact with people and find solutions to anything and everything. I have a big passion to create, either by code or with yarn and paint.

I have been in the hotel industry for many years and I gained so much experineces, from service and handeling different situations to cleaning and building/managing websites and social media channels. It was a journey with a bit of everything.

#### **SKILLS**

- Swedish, English and Cantonese
- Budgeting and cost analysis
- Project Management
- Staff Training
- Digital Marketing
- Wordpress
- Google Analytics
- Meta Business Suite
- Leadership during change
- Process Impovement

#### **CONTACT ME**

Mobile: +46 73 707 27 72 Email: li.gigi89@gmail.com Address: Bryngelshusgatan 99 302 47 Halmstad, Sweden

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Hotel Manager**

Best Western Plus Grand Hotel, 2023 - 2024

Responsible for the business and staff. From housekeeping and the front desk to system and server updates to managing the website and economy.

#### **Reservations Coordinator**

Best Western Plus Grand Hotel, 2017 - 2022

Resposible for group and conference reservations, interface maintenance and social media channels as well as the websites.

#### **Front Desk Agent**

Best Western Plus Grand Hotel, 2015 - 2017

Check in and check out, service and hospitality and reservations.

## **Front Desk Agent**

The Queens Hotel Brighton, 2009

Check in and check out, service and hospitality and reservations.

# **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### **Lund Universitet**

UJIK Utvidgad Juridisk Introduktionskurs, 2014

Extended judicial introduktion course

# Örebro University, Grythytte Akademin

Hotell - och värdskapsprogrammet, 2009 - 2012

Hotel and hospitality program at the finest hotel and restaurant academy githin the Nordic countries.

#### **EF Brighton**

MEHT Master English Hotel Tourism, 2008 - 2009

Master english with subjects: Hotel and Tourism

#### Fredrika Bremergymnasiet

Handelsprogrammet inriktning turism, 2005 - 2008

Commerce with focus on tourism